pandawill.com 2013-04-24

# Security&Privacy policy

**Pandawill's Privacy Policy**

**Security** **：**

Pandawill respects your privacy and takes your online safety seriously. In order to provide you with the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates, we record a variety of information from your visit to our site. We respect your privacy and want you to know about the policies we have in place to protect your personal information.

The policy of allowing access to this Personal Information is only to our staffs with a need to know. We also use available technology and encryption, when legally required or when appropriate for your protection, to provide a more secure environment and to reduce the chance of unauthorized access. Personal Information is stored in a secure environment protected by a combination of physical and technical measures. Tape backups are not permitted to leave the premises without prior authorization..

This information may be collected Register email,Password ，gender  ，shipping and billing address(es), phone number, email address, and credit card number, the date and time, browser and operating system, the URL you request, In addition, we may ask for your country of residence and/or your organization's country of operation, so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations. This information is used for billing, order processing and internal marketing as well as to communicate with you about your order and our site  
When we have more cooperation (like drop shipping), we may collect more information:  
 like Phone number, your website, MSN, your reviews and testimonials etc

**information use:**

**  
** We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may use your personal information internally to collect general information about visitors to this Site, improve Site content and layout, improve our outreach, and market our services and products.

We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our Site and your orders. All customers must provide an email address to allow communication with Pandawill.com regarding orders placed. We may send you a confirmation email after you register with us as well as service-related announcements as necessary (for example, temporary suspension of service for maintenance.) You may also submit your email address to request notification when we receive a new brand, product style or product, or to sign up for our email newsletter and special offers. You can unsubscribe or opt out of future emails at any time (see the Opt Out/Corrections section below for more details).

Like most online retailers, we sometimes use third-party service providers to perform specific functions on our behalf. Any information disclosed to them is solely to help in their provision of service. For example, we provide your name, shipping address, email and phone number to partners such as DHL and UPS in order to guarantee delivery of your orders, and we may use relevant customer information in order to monitor the quality of the third party’s service.  
Similarly, we must provide your credit card number to financial services organizations such as credit card processors and issuers in order to process payments. We protect all submissions of your credit card number for authorization with state-of-the-art data encryption. (More on this below in the Data Security section.)

Notification of updates ******：**

To keep you informed of what information we collect, use, and disclose, we will post any changes or updates to this Privacy Notice on this Site and encourage you to review this Privacy Notice from time to time. Please contact us with any questions about the Privacy Notice.
